<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Keet Seel Erosion</string>
    <string name="privacyText">This is privacy info</string>

    <string name="instructionsText">
        Welcome to the Keet Seel Erosion App!\n
        The purpose of the app is to help Citizen Scientists like you contribute
        to a photo time-series of erosion-sensitive sites in Keet Seel canyon.
        On your hike, will take photos in six locations.  You will upload the photos to our database
        when you return and are connected to wi-fi or cell service. \n\n

        1. Use the map to find each location. You can click the locations to see an example
        photo and a description. Try to match the example photo as best you can.\n\n
        2. Use your phone\'s camera to take a landscape photo.\n\n
        3. Enter the date the photos were taken to enable the select buttons. \n\n
        4. Use the Select buttons to select your photo. Once a photo is selected, the select
        button will turn green and the upload button will be enabled.\n\n
        5. Use the upload buttons when you are connected to the internet. A checkmark will appear
        if the upload was successful.

        </string>



    <string name="loc1Desc">
This photo focuses on the west bank of the stream, facing upstream.
        Use the hill in the top right to try to match the example photo above.

    </string>
    <string name="loc2Desc">This photo includes both banks of the stream, facing downstream.
        Use the rock formations at the center and top of the example image to position your photo.</string>
    <string name="loc3Desc">This location is just to the east of the big waterfall, where the trail goes away from
        the stream. Shoot your photo up the trail, using the rock formations in the example image as a guide. </string>
    <string name="loc4Desc">This photo is looking upstream to the west bank of the stream.
        Use the rock tower formation in the upper right of the example image to guide you.</string>
    <string name="loc5Desc">
        This photo includes both banks of the stream looking downriver.
        Try to match the amount of sky that is included in the example image.
    </string>
    <string name="loc6Desc">This photo is taken at the top of the waterfall area, between the two streams.
        Looking downriver, use the large rock formation at the top of the example image as a guide. </string>
    <string name="locksDesc">No photos are needed at Keet Seel </string>
    <string name="storageSignature">YvS15O5T%2BiS6dOFnt7b10GvOAtKLaTsNSV0WzMcD6YA%3D</string>

</resources>
